(Stuart:)That's beautiful.
(Beverley:)Thank you.
All right, let's continue.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, excuse me,
I need to say something
(Sheldon:)to someone pretty special,
and...
(Sheldon:)I just can't wait any longer.
(Amy:)It's happening.
(Sceme:)Leonard...
(Sheldon:)You and I have
our ups and downs.
(Sheldon:)But I have always considered
you my family.
(Sheldon:)Even before the recent threat
of our parents fornicating
(Sheldon:)like wrinkly old rabbits.
(Sheldon:)I don't always show it, but you
are of great importance to me.
(Sheldon:)Both of you.
(Penny:)Oh...
(Beverley:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
(Bernadette:)And weird other husband who came
with the apartment.